Hello Hello
Today is a sunny day.
It's warm and nice.
We thought we should put in our ...
Boat!
- Boat!
Your boat.
Your old hull, shoulder.
Yes.
This one is like an old abrasive patches.
It's so risky
But it works, and we haven't tested it since I bought it, so we have to test it.
It's about time.
- Yes!
We have driven to a supplementary ramp on the island where we have our summer house.
Here is the car.
Here is the boat.
You see
Yes.
- (Harry) No.
You look pretty good, I think.
It's a little light, so you get a little dazzled.
Here we also have a small treasure.
- (Harry) We will bring it.
Still lucky this happened when I was on the boat, because I think of poor Laura.
(The engine buzzes a little more) Now something is happening.
So I have to sit and pump with the gas for me to have some power from the engine.
It is a sign that there is crap in the carburetor.
We did not end up in sea!
But it was close.
- We ended up at Grandma and Grandpa's jetty.
Yes so far we came today.
Is anyone craving a dip?
I!
- Me too!
1, 2, 3
Was it good?
- Great!
So there.
Now I have called and talked to a good boat meal ...
... and learned that this boat is a little special, so I've learned some tricks.